{
    "subject": "resource/Scooby-Doo!_Pirates_Ahoy!",
    "predicate": "property/starring",
    "object": "resource/Casey_Kasem",
    "human_readable": "Scooby-Doo! Pirates Ahoy! stars Casey Kasem.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7139673829078674,
            "question": "Who is the voice actor for Scooby-Doo! Pirates Ahoy!"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6823525428771973,
            "question": "What movie features Casey Kasem as a voice actor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6177988648414612,
            "question": "What type of adventure does Scooby-Doo! Pirates Ahoy! involve?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6023691892623901,
            "question": "Who are some of the recurring characters in Scooby-Doo!"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5337136387825012,
            "question": "What genre does Scooby-Doo! Pirates Ahoy! belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5222610235214233,
            "question": "In what animated series does Casey Kasem frequently voice a character?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4086306095123291,
            "question": "What is the name of the famous animated mystery-solving group that Casey Kasem has been associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38852861523628235,
            "question": "Why is Casey Kasem considered a notable figure in voice acting?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36890652775764465,
            "question": "What are some common elements found in Scooby-Doo! movies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2520814538002014,
            "question": "What is the name of the iconic talking dog in Scooby-Doo!"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Scooby-Doo! Pirates Ahoy! stars Casey Kasem.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5250_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some common elements found in Scooby-Doo! movies?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5250_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Why is Casey Kasem considered a notable figure in voice acting?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5250_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the famous animated mystery-solving group that Casey Kasem has been associated with?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5250_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5250_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5250_111.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5250_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5250_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5250_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5250_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5250_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5250_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5250_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5250_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "The triple to evaluate is:\n\n\"Scooby-Doo! Pirates Ahoy! stars Casey Kasem.\"\n\nThe relevant documents are:\n\n* file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_5250/re-ranker-msmarco/50.txt\n* file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_5250/re-ranker-msmarco/87.txt\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. The document \"file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_5250/re-ranker-msmarco/50.txt\" mentions Casey Kasem as the voice of Shaggy Rogers in Scooby-Doo, and the document \"file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_5250/re-ranker-msmarco/87.txt\" confirms that Casey Kasem voices Shaggy Rogers in the episode \"Scooby (Frank Welker, who also voices Freddie), Shaggy (Casey Kasem) and the rest of the gang set out on what they hope to be a relaxing, mystery-free cruise.\"\n\nTherefore, the response is:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe document states that \"Casey Kasem voices Norville 'Shaggy' Rogers\" in the context of the Scooby-Doo franchise, which includes episodes like \"Scooby (Frank Welker, who also voices Freddie), Shaggy (Casey Kasem) and the rest of the gang set out on what they hope to be a relaxing, mystery-free cruise.\" This supports the statement that Scooby-Doo! Pirates Ahoy! stars Casey Kasem as Shaggy."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}